Create Hotspot Area
First, Click “CTA Canvas” from left menu
Click “CTA Area Mapping”
Click “Insert a Hotspot Area”
Adjust the box to the correct size and position
Add URL to Hotspot
Click Button “URL” from left menu
Enter a title name
Enter the website URL you want to link
Click to confirm
Click Preview Button on top right
Open the Preview window
Click Hotspot area you created
Now you can access the website you entered
Link to Vinmobi site
Now try to click “Select URL from VinMobi”
Choose one VinMobi Site and Confirm
Click Preview Button on top right
Open the Preview window
Click Hotspot area you created
Now you can access the Vinmobi site you choose
Link to VinDesk site
Now try to click “Select URL from VinDesk”
Choose one VinMobi Site and Confirm
Click Preview Button on top right
Click Hotspot area you created
Now you can access the VinDesk site you choose