Create Hotspot Area
First, Click “CTA Canvas” and “CTA Area Mapping”
Click “Insert a Hotspot Area”
Adjust the box to the correct size and position
Add URL to Hotspot
Click the "URL" button from the left menu
Enter a title name
Enter the website URL you want to link
Click to confirm
Click the "preview" button on the top right
Click hotspot area you created
Now you can access the website you entered
Link to Vinmobi site
Now try to click “Select URL from VinMobi”
Choose a VinMobi Site and Confirm
Click the "preview" button
Open the Preview window
Click hotspot area you created
Now you can access the Vinmobi site you choose
Link to VinDesk site
Now try to click “Select URL from VinDesk”
Choose a VinMobi Site and Confirm
Click the "preview" button on the top right
Click Hotspot area you created
Now you can access the VinDesk site you choose
Hotspot Area Display Settings
First, Create a hotspot area and click “Flicker” on the right
Click to Preview
Now you can see the area of the hotspot flickering
OK, now we can try other display setting
Here change to “Hover”
Click “Preview”
You will see the hotspot doesn't respond until you hover the mouse over it
Here change to “Hidden”
Click “Preview”
This time, the hotspot doesn't respond even when you hover the mouse over it,
but you can still click the hotspot area
Last，let's try hotspot switch method
We use this Photo area as an example
Copy and paste this photo
Now, select a photo we want to switch and put in the copied photo
From here to add this new mask as your favourite
Add a new name, select "asset type" and confirm
Wait until it successes
Select "Hidden" and "Show on Hover"
Click "Set Maker Image" and select the photo you just added
From here, you can set the switched photo position
Click here to preview the result
Confirm and preview webiste
Now you will see the hotspot area switch photo when you hover the mouse over it