Create Hotspot Area
First, Click “CTA Canvas” from left menu
Click “CTA Area Mapping”
Click “Insert a Hotspot Area”
Adjust the box to the correct size and position
Add URL to Hotspot
Click Button “URL” from left menu
Enter a title name
Enter the website URL you want to link
Click to confirm
Click Preview Button on top right
Open the Preview window
Click Hotspot area you created
Now you can access the website you entered
Link to Vinmobi site
Now try to click “Select URL from VinMobi”
Choose one VinMobi Site and Confirm
Click Preview Button on top right
Open the Preview window
Click Hotspot area you created
Now you can access the Vinmobi site you choose
Link to VinDesk site
Now try to click “Select URL from VinDesk”
Choose one VinMobi Site and Confirm
Click Preview Button on top right
Click Hotspot area you created
Now you can access the VinDesk site you choose
Hotspot Area Display Settings
First, Create a hotspot area
Click “Flicker” on the right
Click “Click” on the right
Click to Preview
Now you can see the area of the hotspot flickering
OK, now we can try other display setting
Here change to “Hover”
Click “Preview”
You will see the hotspot doesn't respond until you hover the mouse over it
Here change to “Hidden”
Click “Preview”
This time hotspot doesn't respond even you hover the mouse over it
But you still can click the hotspot area
Now let’s see how the hotspot switch method
We use this Photo area as an example
First, copy and paste this photo
Now, select a photo we want to switch and put in the copied photo
From here to add this new mask as your favourite
Add a new name, select asset type and confirm
Wait until it successes
Select Hidden and Show on Hover
Click “Set Maker Image” and select the photo you added just now
From here, you can set the switched photo position
Press here to preview the result
Now, confirm and preview the result
Now you will see the hotspot area switch photo when you hover the mouse over it